// contains questions as js array
// each question is an object

var questions = [
  {
    question: "Which year was the premier league founded?",
    options: ["1998", "1992", "1989", "1990"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which club won the 2017 UEFA Super cup?",
    options: ["Real madrid", "ABC", "WER", "Y78"],
    answer: 1,
  },
   {
    question: "Which Dutch player was voted 'European Player of the Century' ?",
    options: ["John", "Ronaldo", " Johan Cruyff", "Peter"],
    answer: 3,
  },
   {
    question: "Which English referee officiated the 2010 World Cup final?",
    options: ["John", "Ronaldo", " Johan Cruyff", "Eric Cantona"],
    answer: 3,
  },
   {
    question: "Who is the world's most expensive teenager?",
    options: ["Peter", "Onel", " Kylian Mbappe", "Steel"],
    answer: 3,
  },
   {
    question: " Who is the oldest manager in Premier League history?",
    options: ["Roy Hodgson ", "Troy", " Hudson", "Steel"],
    answer: 1,
  },
   {
    question: " Who scored the first Premier League hat-trick?",
    options: ["Eric ", "Troy", " Hudson", "Steel"],
    answer: 1,
  },
   {
    question: " Who holds the record for most consecutive Premier League appearances (310)?",
    options: ["Vin ", "Troy", " Brad", "Steel"],
    answer: 3,
  },
   {
    question: " Who was manager of Manchester City when they won their first Premier League title?",
    options: ["Vin ", "Nevon", " Brad", "Robert"],
    answer: 4,
  },
   {
    question: " Which team saw themselves eliminated from the 2018 World Cup due to fair play rules?",
    options: ["Senegal ", "ABC", " J78", "987"],
    answer: 1,
  },
];
